맙소사!
Oh my gosh!
내가 야만인인 걸 모르시나요?
Don't you know I’m a Savage?
나는 킬라애
I’m a Killa who will break you, ae
여전히 비밀스럽고 환상을 보여주는 너
You're still hiding and hallucinating
Hit We Holler
Beat you up, We Holler
겁없는 너 너 더 세게 때려
I'm not afraid of you, you, Hit you harder
나에 대한 딥 페이크
Push me in, Deep fake on me
아직 준비되지 않은 단계로 밀어붙이기
To the unprepared stage
Corner me in, Fake on me
나에 대한 가짜
모두가 나를 조롱하게 만들었어
Got everybody mock up to me
부끄럽게 만들고 마음을 흔들게 해
You shake me up so that I feel ashamed
무관심한 관객붕괴 ae
Cold spectators are collapsed, ae
더 이상 참을 수 없어 Say No!
I can't stand you anymore, Say No!
두고 보자, 난 좀 야만적이야
Wait and see, I'm a little Savage
너의 더러운 플레이
Your Dirty Play
더 이상 가만히 앉아 있을 수 없어
I can't stand it any longer
당신은 내 환상을 파괴하고 싶어
You want to break me
Your hallucinations are becoming
점차적으로 그것은 당신을 세우는 이유가 됩니다
the reasons to construct you
I’m a Savage
나는 야만인이다
널 짓밟아줄게 Oh
I'll break you into pieces Oh
나는 야만인이다
I’m a Savage
짓밟아버릴 거야 Oh
I'll crush you Oh
지금 나를 잡아라 나를 잡아라
Get me get me now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
지금 나를 잡아
Get me now
그렇지 않으면 나는 더 야만인이 될 것이다
Or I'll become more Savage
지금 나를 잡아라 나를 잡아라
Get me get me now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
이제 난 널 잡으러 왔어
Now I'm going to get you
이제 나는 야만인이다
Now I'm a Savage
지금 줘 줘
Gimme gimme now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
네가 말한 걸 봤어
I can see your words
당신의 약점 알고리즘
Your weakness Algorithm
더위가 쑥쑥 빠져나가
Steaming, it's steaming
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
방해하지마 MA ae SYNK
MA ae SYNK
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
길을 잃다 새비지
음 다들 나만 쳐다봐
Mmmh Everybody looks at me
매우 친숙하지 않나요?
I'm used to it
포기하세요. 어른처럼 참으세요.
I should take a step back, I have to endure it like an adult
나는 유리 안에 갇혀 있어요
I'm locked up in the glass
난 아직도 놀고 싶어
I want to play
그런 끔찍한 기대
Such a horrible expectation
그 환상의 틀 속에 나를 가두었지
I'm locked up in that hallucination frame
KWANGYA Game in을 향해 갑니다
I'm going to KWANGYA, Game in
교묘한 소외 계획을 물리치세요
Defeating a subtle alienation
그리고 내 시작은 ae에서 점차 멀어져가네
And making me drift apart from my ae
속셈이 있는 너 Trick
Your satisfying Trick
우리는 KWANGYA 게임을 향해 갔다
We gone KWANGYA, Game in
내 빛의 검을 베어라
Cut it down, my sword of light
당하는 당신에게
To you who is damaged
자비 없이 공격하라
It's a merciless punch
두고 보자, 난 좀 야만적이야
See? I'm a little Savage
당신의 재생을 차단
I block your regenerative power
엉망 제거
I distract you, I leave you out
잊지 마세요 여긴 KWANGYA입니다
Don't forget, this is KWANGYA
당신의 시간과 공간을 내가 원하는 대로 조절할 수 있어요
I control your time and space
그것을 깨뜨리게 해라
Make It break it
나는 야만인이다
I’m a Savage
널 짓밟아줄게 Oh
I'll break you into pieces Oh
나는 야만인이다
I’m a Savage
짓밟아버릴 거야 Oh
I'll crush you Oh
지금 나를 잡아라 나를 잡아라
Get me get me now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
지금 나를 잡아
Get me now
그렇지 않으면 나는 더 야만인이 될 것이다
Or I'll become more Savage
지금 나를 잡아라 나를 잡아라
Get me get me now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
이제 난 널 잡으러 왔어
Now I'm going to get you
이제 나는 야만인이다
Now I'm a Savage
지금 줘 줘
Gimme gimme now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
네가 말한 걸 봤어
I can see your words
당신의 약점 알고리즘
Your weakness Algorithm
더위가 쑥쑥 빠져나가
Steaming, it's steaming
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
방해하지마 MA ae SYNK
MA ae SYNK
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
길을 잃다 새비지
위기에 처했을 때 나를 지켜주는 건 너야
You are the one who protected me when I was in trouble
내 네비스, 우리는 당신을 사랑해요
My naevis we love U
나의 승리 SYNK DIVE 올인원
My victory, one SYNK DIVE
모두 당신이 만들어낸 기회다
All the opportunities you've created
난 네 희생을 알아 Oh
I know your sacrifices Oh
내 네비스, 우리는 당신을 사랑해요
My naevis we love U
나는 우리가 당신의 기억을 찾는 데 도움이 될 것이라는 것을 알고 있습니다
I know, we'll make sure to find your memories
우리는 부활 후에 만나야 합니다
Let's meet surely after the resurrection
야만적인
Savage
응~
Yeah~
지금 나를 잡아라 나를 잡아라
Get me get me now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
지금 나를 잡아
Get me now
그렇지 않으면 나는 더 야만인이 될 것이다
Or I'll become more Savage
지금 나를 잡아라 나를 잡아라
Get me get me now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
이제 난 널 잡으러 왔어
Now I'm going to get you
이제 나는 야만인이다
Now I'm a Savage
지금 줘 줘
Gimme gimme now
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
네가 말한 걸 봤어
I can see your words
당신의 약점 알고리즘
Your weakness Algorithm
더위가 쑥쑥 빠져나가
Steaming, it's steaming
(쭈쭈쭈쭈)
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
방해하지마 MA ae SYNK
MA ae SYNK
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
길을 잃다 새비지
하하, 뭐?
Ha ha, What?